{
    "subject": "resource/Chandidas_Mahavidyalaya",
    "predicate": "property/type",
    "object": "Undergraduate college",
    "human_readable": "Chandidas Mahavidyalaya is an undergraduate college.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9326909780502319,
            "question": "What type of institution is Chandidas Mahavidyalaya?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8903585076332092,
            "question": "Does Chandidas Mahavidyalaya offer graduate programs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8125424385070801,
            "question": "Who might attend Chandidas Mahavidyalaya?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7657173275947571,
            "question": "What subjects are likely offered at Chandidas Mahavidyalaya?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.723351776599884,
            "question": "What are the typical student demographics at Chandidas Mahavidyalaya?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6586765646934509,
            "question": "At what level of education does Chandidas Mahavidyalaya primarily teach?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5575552582740784,
            "question": "Where is Chandidas Mahavidyalaya located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5316265225410461,
            "question": "Are there any notable alumni from Chandidas Mahavidyalaya?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.460009902715683,
            "question": "What is the reputation of Chandidas Mahavidyalaya in its region?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3748778998851776,
            "question": "What are some extracurricular activities offered at Chandidas Mahavidyalaya?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Chandidas Mahavidyalaya is an undergraduate college.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1264_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the reputation of Chandidas Mahavidyalaya in its region?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1264_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable alumni from Chandidas Mahavidyalaya?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1264_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Chandidas Mahavidyalaya located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1264_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1264_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1264_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1264_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1264_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1264_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1264_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1264_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1264_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1264_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1264_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here's my evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while Chandidas Mahavidyalaya is indeed a college (a government affiliated college, to be precise), there is no specific mention in the documents that it is an undergraduate college. The documents do mention courses such as B.A., B.Sc (Honours & General) and Undergraduate (UG) B.A, B.Sc (Honours & General) courses, but they don't explicitly state that Chandidas Mahavidyalaya is a solely undergraduate institution."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Chandidas Mahavidyalaya being a college that offers undergraduate courses such as B.A. (Hons) in Sanskrit, B.A. in Political Science, and others. This supports the statement that Chandidas Mahavidyalaya is an undergraduate college."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Chandidas Mahavidyalaya offers postgraduate courses like Sanskrit Under Graduate - B.A. (Hons)-Bachelor of Arts (Honors) which indicates that the college has a higher-level educational program beyond undergraduate level.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}